No living creature was hurt during
the filming of this series.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com
Come on, Alps!
Stay together!
-Mother!
-Fatma!
Nayman!
I kill those who touch my daughter!
Fatma, come. Come.
-Run. Run without looking back!
-Mother...
Fatma! Listen to me!
Run without looking back! Come on!
Fatma!
Malhun.. Malhun!
Go after Fatma. I'll stay here, come on! Go!
Fatma!
If we die, we die for this cause..
...if we survive we survive for this cause.
But we will live today.
Allah is the greatest!
Kayis are rising against the cruel!
The world will bow down before them!
Allah is the greatest!
That's how you run.
That's how you will run.
-Are you alright?
-I am alright.
Allah is the greatest!
Search around!
Dress the wounds of those who are injured.
Aykurt...
-Are you alright?
-I am alright, my Bey.
Samil. Are you alright?
I am alright, my Bey.
I am alright.
Come on, go check the injured ones.
And take him to Yenisehir.
That was the vanguard.
Their intention..
...is to open a road for the ones behind.
But... we ruined their move, my Bey.
We did.
We did, but...
...they will start attacking us.
They can come, my Bey! They can come!
We asked for gaza when we turned
these lands into our homeland.
We will unite.
We will destroy their courage.
This land is a homeland for our friends...
...and a graveyard for our enemies.
Come on Alps. Come on.
- In the name of Allah
- Come on, brother.
This is the place Boran told us.
But they are not here. Where do you think they are?
We'll find them Ayse. We will. Come on, this way.
Come on!
Fatma!
Bala mother..
-Mother!
-My daughter!
Hang on!
We are going back!
-My daughter!
-Mother!
Thank Allah.
Malhun. Are you alright?
We are alright.
My Fatma.
-You are injured.
-It's not important.
Malhun... BoranJ are you alright?
Yes, Bala Hatun, I am.
Stay here. We will go after them.
No. I won't leave you alone.
Malhun, you will stay here for your children.
Alps! Come on! Go after them!
Come on brothers! Come on!
Mother... You are bleeding.
It's not deep, don't worry.
My Fatma.
Bring them to the place I'll tell you.
Go. Come Bala..
Come. I will bury you all in this forest!
Fatma!
May Allah bless you, where are you?
You've played enough. Come out, Fatma!
Fatma!
My daughter, Fatma!
She is not here!
-No. We looked everywhere. She is not here.
-Where did she go?
She is not in here. If she was, we would find her.
What if she left the mansion?
I swear not, Ulgen Hatun. We are not even
letting birds pass, we would see her.
The doors are closed.
Where did that child go then?
Mother..
What if she left in Malhun Hatun's carriage?
My Allah, protect us.
Attention! Osman Bey is coming!
Come on!
Baysungur, take the wounded
to the healing house.
As you wish, Bey.
My little sheep.
Quickly, quickly!
Where's everyone?
Bey.
You're hurt as well.
Go in and we will take a look.
No, it is not important.
It is not important, however,
where is everyone?
My Bey, Esrigun Hatun and Boran Alp.
They fell in Nayman's trap.
Malhun Ha tun and Bala Hatun..
Went after them.
What are you saying?
Take Halime.
Alps, everyone that can hold
a sword comes with me.
Dress your wounds.
-Let us go.
-Bey.
Another thing.
VAIIah I don't know where she went, however..
Fatma.
We can't find her anywhere...
We looked everywhere but...
-She's missing.
-What are you saying
How is she missing?
How is Fatma missing?
What are you doing here?
How can you look after such a small child, tell me?
Bey, I never let her out of my sight.
She is missing since Malhun Hatun went.
I have an idea, however..
Bey, we thought perhaps she went
with the carriage that Malhun Hatun got on.
My Fatma..
Bey father, don't you miss us?
Of course I do.
I feel pain at the tip of my nose
whenever I don't see you.
You say so, but you always
take my brothers to the battle.
You don't take us at all.
My dear daughter.
My beautiful daughter,
look Halime cannot walk yet.
So you need to help her, take care of her.
Alps.
Everyone to their horses.
My heart takes me to enemy's hands.
Quickly.
You dog.
Boran.
Are you alright?
I am alright Bala Hatun.
Can you hold on?
I can, with Allah's permission.
Alright.
-Thank you.
-Let us go.
This way, tracks lead this way.
Alps, sisters, this way.
Let us go.
Fatma, what are you doing here?
Why did you come?
We were going to the tribe, how should I know..
That you were going into the fight.
Are you alright?
Do you have any other wounds?
-Are you hurt?
-No.
Osman.
-Malhun.
-Osman.
-Father.
-Fatma.
My child.
My dear.
-Father.
-My dear.
My dear.
-You're alright?
-I was so scared, father.
Malhun.
-Malhun.
-Osman.
-I am alright, don't worry.
-Are you alright? Your leg
-I am alright
We are alright.
Osman, Nayman escaped.
Catch up to them,
Boran and Bala went after them.
He won't escape, don't worry.
Aktemur, to the horses.
Nayman won't escape.
We will deal with him now.
This forest will be their grave today, Bey.
It will, quickly now.
You go to Yenisehir.
-Quickly, quickly now.
-Let us go.
Today, all of you are going to die.
It's your blood that is going to
fall on the ground today, Nayman.
We're going to kill you for
a single drop of Fatma's blood.
We're outnumbered.
They drew us into a trap.
Are you afraid, Esrigun Hatun?
I'm not worried about myself, but you, Boran Alp.
You have sword wounds all around.
They are like just fly bites to me.
Don't worry.
There is no way out of here.
Bless me!
-You have it.
You have it, Ayse!
Then... In the name of Allah!
-Allah is the greatest!
-Attack!
Allah is the greatest!
Keep Bala's head, though!
We'll send it to Osman.
Well, Osman's hatun..
It seems it's your blood
that will be shed today.
Death is a right for us, Nayman!
It can't fear us.
I'll send your head to Osman...
..in silk fabrics.
Osman.
Aktemur.
Nayman!
Today, your head is going to fall!
-Come to me!
-Nokers.
Attack!
Bursa Palace
Lord Valens will make you pay for this.
Where do you think you are going?
To Lefke.
I sent horsemen as a precaution first.
Now I'm going to rule my castle.
We can't leave Gemlik unprotected
while Turks are harassing us.
We're going to leave here.
Lord would understand.
Understand what exactly, Lord?
Why I'm going back to Koyunhisar.
The reason why we are going back
to our castles and citadels, sir.
What's going on here?
Sir Valens, bad news reached Bursa before you.
Go ahead.
Osman and his beys are alive.
The vanguard got destroyed.
Osman!
He destroyed Jesus' chosen troop.
I'll be baptized with his blood.
When I kill Osman
...he won't even have a grave to be buried in.
I will smash his bones!
And you?
You're going back to your castles like cowards.
Fools.
Now I see better..
...how those shepherds have beaten you...
..for years.
Go hide behind the walls.
Cowards who are afraid of fighting.
We'll fight.
Nayman and I will unite our armies.
We'll take our lands back.
You attacked..
...my house and children, huh?
You think I'll leave you like this?
Come here. I will..
I will... I will..
I will take your everything.
You will have only your life left.
Come.
Come here. Come.
You will pay for what you did.
Come.
Get up! Get up!
You will pay.
Get up!
I'm going to survive this too.
Then I will spit on you.
Where are you going to go, ha?
Where are you going to go?
You think I'll leave you?
You can't go anywhere!
Which commanders will turn against...
..after you fall?
You'll give me all the names.
Come here.
All of them will fight to avenge me.
But you can't kill me.
Osman..
Esrigun won't let that happen.
You say so, huh?
You say so?
Now..
Stand up.
Here..
I'm both the Bey and the state.
And only I can decide...
...who is going to die.
Now give me the names of the commanders.
Come on!
A great army...
will come
after you.
Those who hate Gazan.
Even if I die, they will keep fighting...
...and make this place a homeland for them.
Come.
I'll let them know too, don't worry.
I'll bury the one who sets eye on my lands
under the ground of my lands.
Bury them Osman, bury them.
When I get back from Tebriz,
I'll bury you too.
Do you think I'll let you go?
You can't go anywhere.
Osman Bey.
Nayman's head is Gazan Khan's right.
He will be taken to Tebriz with a solid troop.
Gazan Khan wants to receive Nayman alive.
Osman Bey.
I'm not talking in vain.
You will follow the orders of Gazan Khan
who saved you from such chaos.
You do not deserve to take Nayman's head.
As Esrigun Hatun wishes.
Come here Ayaz.
-Yes my Bey.
-Alps!
You will go to Nayman's outpost.
Guards will stay there.
Don't let anyone get inside.
We will go to Yenisehir.
Come on, get him up.
Folks
Don't forget,
these two great armies will unite.
Sir.
Sir, Osman cornered Nayman.
He will capture him soon.
Capturing Nayman won't be enough for Osman.
He will want more as his ancestors.
Osman wants to take our castles.
We should go to our castles and take precautions.
Lords!
We will no longer hide behind the walls
and defend them!
We will attack.
We will destroy Turks in a battlefield.
How can we do it without Nayman's army, Lord Valens?
I will go to Constantinople.
I will ask for his army from Emperor Andronikos.
If we save Nayman,
we will not need Emperor's support.
No one can save Nayman from Osman anymore.
Nayman is a dead man.
Soon, I'll take Osman's life, his people
I'll take everything from him.
Leo, get the horses ready.
Move!
-Look at him!
-Move.
Move.
Move! Come on!
Move!
I'll kill them all.
Infidel!
-Punish him!
-Just wait.
Just wait, hang on.
Comparison to what you did,
this is nothing.
Wait.
I will not let you
walk towards your death.
Open up.
What's this Osman Bey?
Everyone gets what they deserve.
Come on.
Come to your end.
Come.
Come here.
Walk.
Move.
Folks!
Here
here's the dastard Nayman,
who is the head of
many oppressions and evil tricks.
Now
Esrigun Hatun says that
Gazan Khan
deserves to take his head.
But I say that the best enemy
is the one who is under the ground.
He tortured my people.
He shed blood of my people.
From now on
his blood
is our right.
The price of what you're doing
will be very heavy, Osman Bey.
Nayman will get to Tebriz.
Gazan Khan will punish him.
No, no.
I will never let him get away from me again.
The only thing that will go to Gazan Khan
will be this dastard's head.
My death
will cause vengeance to emerge, Osman.
Holy war is bigger than vengeance.
Whoever sets eyes on our lands
will be ruined.
Your head
will be a warning for them.
Osman Bey.
Gok Teng
I fought for you.
I will die for you.
But
everything
will be done in order.
Your time has come.
What did you do Osman Bey?
I did what was necessary.
Without even thinking about it.
You hunted Gazan Khan's prey.
How are you going to answer him?
The prey does not belong
to the one who laid his eyes on it...
...but to the one who beheads it.
Tell this to Gazan Khan.
Boran. Bring that head.
Come here.
Here..
...another cruel's head fell down.
But there are still many of them!
They are all waiting for us in ambush.
Now..
...we will attack before they attack.
Now the conquests won't stop.
Alps! Send news to all houses...
...to all tribes, to all places!
All valiants who can hold swords...
..will stand next to us.
Yes my Bey!
Turks' sanjaks...
...will gather under one sanjak now.
And we will come for the cruel!
Allah is the greatest!
Long live Osman Bey!
Stop, wait a second brother.
What happened brother?
You look like a groom.
Is there something we don't know?
What groom are you talking about, brother?
You are the groom.
O, you are the one
who looks too much of a groom.
He thinks everyone is like him.
No, brother.
There is something different about you. Cerkutay is right.
Brother, what can I do?
Should I wear cheap clothes and
look careless in front of those people, Konur?
No, sure. Look at yourself.
You are a man who looks like a mountain.
You might become a groom of a Khan anytime.
I can teach you Mongolian once in a while, Boran.
You might need it.
Brother, you are making fun of me.
Come on. Come on, brother. My Bey is waiting for us.
Come on. Go.
Our Bey is waiting for us...
...but there must be someone else waiting for you. Right?
You really had fun here, brothers.
-Confess.
-Come on.
Come on, Cerkutay. Move. Move.
Brother, move!
Brother... Aren't you going to tell us...
...how you saved Esrigun Hatun.
So?
Brothers... May Allah let me end up
at the edge of Dark Midwife's staff.
At least it's better than
being a prey in your chat!
Please. The grass looks greener on the other side.
Come on, my Bey is waiting.
Come on! Come on brothers!
Brother, we are going to attend the meeting, you'll come later.
We are going, you will attend later.
How is your wound, Boran Alp?
I am alright, thanks to Allah.
I've experienced worse ones, Esrigun Hatun.
I... could not thank you
since I was dealing with...
...so many things.
It's not a problem, Esrigun Hatun.
I just did my duty.
No. You did more than your duty.
I owe you my life now.
No, Esrigun Hatun. No.
You do not owe me.
Besides, I did what I was told.
This is yours.
No, Esrigun Hatun. I cannot accept this.
It's my gift, Boran Alp.
How can one return gifts?
Thank you.
Live long.
You protected me...
...and may this protect you when you feel weak.
My Bey is waiting for me. I should go to him.
Thank you.
I... am the littlest son of the dynasty...
...Valens Leon.
I was born as a Mouzalon.
And I've fought for years as a Mouzalon.
My family made great armies kneel.
They defeated people who were called "invincible".
It was all for you, Holy Jesus.
You tamed me.
They took the fearsome Mouzalon..
And made me Lord Valens.
Priest.
I want to be re-baptised.
I want to reincarnate..
As Commander Mouzalon.
Come, my son.
Do you believe that..
Jesus is your saviour and your God?
Yes.
May this holy water reincarnate you, Mouzalon.
I baptise you, in the name of..
Our God, Jesus Christ and
The Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Jesus Christ.
Bless me.
Bless me, so I can
spill the blood of Turks.
I am reborn as..
Commander Mouzalon.
My dear daughter.
Festival of my heart.
What if something happened to you?
What would I do then?
Could I live without you?
What, my new sibling would come.
Where are my shoes anyway?
Did you throw them away so suddenly?
Of course not.
Are you..
Talking about these bychance?
Yes, I am talking about those, Osman Bey.
Did you get them from the roof?
No, not roof.
I had them made for you.
However..
If you don't come have dinner with me..
I won't give these to you.
Good, then my growing sibling can wear them.
I am not hungry anyway.
Look at you.
You two keep talking.
And I will have a look at the table.
Maybe Fatma would be hungry by then.
My beautiful dear.
My beauty.
Look at you.
What if something happened to you?
What if I never saw you again?
Then what would I had done, tell me?
You already don't see me Osman Bey,
you only see your Alps.
You only see Iltutan.
Even you see your enemies more than us.
You either go to battle or work for battle.
Will you be always Osman Bey?
When will you be our Bey Father?
Come here.
I am your father.
Of course I am your father.
I am Osman Bey sometimes..
And your Bey Father the other times.
I was very scared father.
I was very scared.
I want to see my father more.
My dear.
Do you know why you can't see me?
So that your children can born to a strong state.
Don't you think that
I want to see you every second?
However..
However, now this well.
We do not live for ourselves.
Our only concern is the Divine Word.
Our fight is for Islam Nation.
In this road..
The longing we have for our home and children..
Is our greatest challenge.
Do you also miss us?
Of course I do.
Of course.
However..
I don't think you miss me.
Because if you did..
You would've come to dinner with me.
Let's go before food gets cold, Bey Father.
My dear, that's it.
That's it.
Let us go.
My dear Fatma.
Since she found her father she shows coyness.
She does of course.
Did you already forget
what she did until Halime came?
Of course not.
However, when Halime was seen
all went out to be well.
These are sweet coyness,
right Halime?
Thank Allah.
She is very beautiful, praise be.
May her destiny is well also.
-Amen.
Amen.
May the same happen to you soon as well,
Esrigun Hatun.
However, you should be quick.
Brothers will be fine tomorrow,
right Dark Midwife?
My mother made soup with her own hands.
Of course they will be alright, brother.
My mother's hands heal.
Oh lunatic boy, oh!
You have a gift for gab.
You are something else!
He, Dark Midwife...
He is a dark horse, my brother.
He may be a dark horse..
But he is mine now.
Stop messing with my brother.
He has just became a groom.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Praise be, praise be!
May your chat be plenteous.
My little lamb.
Come.
Come here.
-Through here.
-Come my beautiful daughter.
You may sit.
-Another enemy head fell off my Bey.
-That's right.
We cut another enemy's head as well.
But there are thousands more ahead.
Fatma Sultan.
It is not the time to talk about battle.
Now Osman Bey is gone
Father Osman is here right, father?
That's right.
My Halime.
Come here now.
What's that? Are you going to
grow up and go to battle?
No. Come on now.
Get into the middle with your spoon.
Come on, come on walk.
Come on, before battle...
So you almost went to the battle, is that so?
But you are too little for battle now.
My Halime, come here.
No, don't. I did it, but you stay away from it sister.
We're not ready for battle yet.
I'm glad that Ulgen sister held Halime.
I wish I had been more careful and
I had caught you too Fatma.
Don't play games without my knowledge again.
I will not tell anyone, all right?
I said tawba, I'd
never do that again.
It's not like the trainings at all.
Of course it's not, my angel daughter.
In battle, you have your enemies against you,
in training, you have your brothers.
My brothers let me breathe
but they would not wait for me
to breathe in battle, right?
They would not, Fatma.
That is why you need to train
yourself in a great way.
Right. Oh my beautiful daughter.
Halime.
Come here, come.
Come here. Come here.
Let's eat, enjoy your meal.
My Bala.
Give her to me my Bey. Come here daughter.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Any news from Baysungur?
We got news my Bey he want to take it.
Very well.
So, Dark Midwife, tell me
whose turn is it for wedding?
Is there anyone on your mind?
There is my Bey, there is.
There is someone in my mind.
However
it's too soon right now.
Well done brother.
Well done.
Start collecting gold right now.
It is too hard to collect them later on.
Cerkutay.
You look naive, but you're such a rascal.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in Baysungu
My Bey, we got a message from Marthaleus.
Osman Bey, Lord Valens came to Constantinople.
I'm following his every step as you ordered.
Fatma.
It's time for Bey Osman.
Alps, inform Beys...
-We'll have the council.
-As you order, my Bey.
Lord Valens, welcome.
Emperor didn't know you would come.
-If you...
-Unexpected things are happening to me too!
We are losing...
...our soldiers, lands and Byzantine.
I have no time to lose.
Let Emperor know!
Sure, Lord Valens.
Not Valens..
...but Mouzalon, the Butcher of Turks is here.
My Bey, beys are here.
May they come in?
Let them in.
Come in, beys.
Welcome.
Tell me.
What's the situation in the lands
the wolf set his eyes on?
My Bey.
Forgive me, but...
For this at this time?
Well, be patient.
Let's speak of the good first.
We will..
..talk about the bad too.
Uraz Bey, speak.
They're fortifying the defense in Kestel Castle.
They were sure the troop
that had come would hit us.
Now they are afraid.
They should be.
They must also have heard
Nayman lost his head.
Well, well..
What about..
..Lefke and Gemlik?
They are digging pits on the roads to Gemlik.
They're laying traps in the woods.
But we know where they are.
It's the same for Lefke, my Bey.
They know the inevitable.
Their lands will belong to Turks soon.
Thank you.
There is still time for these.
It's time to speak of the bad.
Lord Valens..
...went to Constantinople in haste.
He lost Nayman. He lost the commanders.
He lost the troop that
he surely thought would kill us.
He went to Constantinople...
...to gain strength.
If he succeeds..
..comes back with an army
..then..
...we will have a tough battle.
I'm ignoring the disrespect of your entrance.
What do you want, Valens?
That's exactly why I'm here, Emperor.
Even your aide is whining like a kid.
For God's sake
...what does Byzantine have?
Where is the Roman spirit?
Where are the powerful men?
Everyone hides like a woman...
..and whines like a kid.
I will...
...save Byzantine from the Turks.
Give the lordship to your whining politicians.
I will take your army.
And as before
...I will lead the army as Commander Mouzalon.
Tell me what happened.
Osman killed Nayman.
He destroyed my troops.
And now he's preparing to march
to Koyunhisar and Lefke.
I will destroy him in a pitched battle.
Osman helped me a lot.
But if he has set his eyes on our lands,
...we will scratch his eyes out.
You already asked for an army from your friends
in the west without asking me. Lord Valens.
I'm not a Lord anymore.
I'm the commander of Byzantine army.
I will destroy Osman's dreams.
By capturing Koyunhisar,
...he's trying to disconnect Bursa from Iznik.
Osman is besieging us more every passing day.
Give your army..
...under my command. Emperor.
When I last gave the army to Prince Kantakouzenos,
..he threatened my throne.
How will I know you won't do the same?
I am the man...
...who got threatened by spears
on his neck!
...for the glory of Byzantine.
I am not a man who wants throne...
..but a man who leaves a title for Byzantine.
You must trust me, Emperor.
If you didn't, it would be a huge mistake.
Soldiers.
You will have the army, Commander Mouzalon.
If Osman attempts to destroy us,
...you will respond to him the way he deserves.
Mighty Emperor.
I intend to..
...destroy Osman in Bafeus Plains...
...where is he advancing.
For this reason
...we need to prepare an army
consisted of the best soldiers.
Leo, get prepared.
Soldiers will met Commander Mouzalon.
My Bey, if he gets the army
..what will we do?
Whatever army he recruits
...we won't stop.
As I said,
..Lefke, Kestel and Gemlik.
These will wait for now.
But not Koyunhisar.
We didn't send messages to villages in vain.
We didn't send message to tribes in vain.
With the troops to be recruited there,
...we will be an one-body army.
And we'll march to Koyunhisa
My Bey.
Do you have any information about the army...
...which will come from Constantinople?
We don't know how many
or how well they are equipped.
We should know about the army first.
So we'll know if we should..
...hit and run or fight in a pitch.
My Bey, is this the right time for a siege?
Just be patient.
Be patient.
In Constantinople,
...we have an intelligence service.
They told us that Lord Valens went there.
Now they will tell us...
...what he's going to do next.
And by that time,
...you'll have finished the preparations.
My Bey
...if we are caught during the siege,
...they will destroy us.
I said we would take Koyunhisar.
I didn't say we'd besiege it.
If we are to fight in the pitch,
...we'll fight.
If we are to lay an ambush,
...we will lay an ambush.
If we are to retreat
..we will retreat.
But I never conquer..
...according to the moves of heathens.
As my Bey orders.
The council is over.
Beys.
Now listen to me carefully.
The army that will come against us...
..is the most difficult test..
...we will ever experience.
We will..
...fight...
...against the Byzantine army...
...as the owners of this border alone.
The thing that succeeds
in defeating the empire...
..is the state now.
Don't forget this.
You can go.
Do you know me?
Commander Mouzalon.
They always tell your stories at quarters.
Good.
Now a new legend will be written...
...at my command.
You will experience what you've heard.
We will send Turks away from
these lands forever, Commander Mouzalon.
Bad times come, soldier.
Bad times..
...bring strong men.
Strong men fight.
And they bring peaceful days.
But... peaceful days...
...bring weak men.
Those weak and miserable men...
...bring bad times again.
We know who the weak men are.
Then who are..
..the ones who will bring
the Byzantium to its feet again?
We are!
We are.
They made Byzantium kneel.
And we will make it stronger than before.
Commanders.
May your swords be sharper than a lion's paw.
You will leave the city without being seen.
When you arrive in Osman's lands...
..you will unite with the other army...
...and turn into the furor of hell.
We will fight for Byzantium!
We were born for Byzantium..
...and we can die for Byzantium.
-For Byzantium.
I am going back to Bursa.
You will bring death after me.
May Allah salute you.
O, Magnificent...
...O, retributive justice!
...O, my Allah, who resolves things.
You made us responsible...
..for the war..
...for the battle.
And we are trying hard to...
...deserve being on Your way, my Allah.
The victory...
..and the defeat..
...comes from You, my Allah.
O, the Most Merciful..
..O my Creator..
Tomorrow, we will set out on a difficult road.
Enlighten our way, my Allah.
My Allah...
...do not test us with an ending
which will make the cruel laugh, my Allah.
My Allah..
May You grant us a victory which will...
...make the oppressed smile and
Muslims experience the joy of bairam.
My Allah.
For the sake of the the messenger of Allah
(PBUH) Nabi...
...and the ones close to Allah..
...allow us to enlighten the...
...darkness of the infidels
with the light of Islam, O my Allah.
My Allah...
The valiants behind me..
..are the soldiers of Islam's army.
Grant us with the fate of Your ashabs...
..who were victorious in Badr and Khaybar.
Grant us..
...so that we can be granted with
establishing a state that will...
...place the sanjak of Islam all over the world.
My Allah...
Grant us with a...
...glorious victory.
Ameen, my Allah.
Load it.
May it be easy sisters.
Thank you Malhun Hatun.
Keep your eyes wide open.
A mistake would cause someone to die.
Thank you for your works Hatuns.
Thank you Malhun Hatun.
May our holy war be mubarak.
If Allah permits, Malhun Hatun.
Praise be!
Look how she's working.
She is my woman after all.
You rascal!
Why are you standing still?
-Mother?
-Mother.
Of course!
Take water there and take it to Ulgen.
Help her a bit.
Instead of just looking, do some work!
There's a battle ahead!
Come on! Come on!
-My Ulgen.
-Yes, my Cerkutay?
Today,
you look so beautiful.
-Really?
-Really.
You too
you look like a soldier.
You know, don't make me talk about it.
Should I put some bulgur in it?
All right, go get it.
Go Cerkutay! Go now, go!
You're doing work but you're
looking at Ulgen at the same time.
-Come on, come on!
-Mother, but...
Go away!
Go and do some other work.
All right but we just married.
Ulgen, your mother won't let us be alone.
All right, don't worry.
May Allah make
your conversation last forever.
Aameen.
How can we do work with them?
We say there's battle ahead.
Do you trust your double sword?
Try to get along.
I trust your prayers, mother!
Angel mother.
But I guess you're tired,
that's why you're so grumpy.
Have a seat, if you want.
You're old after all.
-What am I?
-Mother!
He said you're too tired, mother.
Right, Malhun Hatun?
Now, since we will be behind Osman Bey,
they are coming from all over,
O praise be!
We need to cook lots of food.
Praise be!
We will make it on time for sure!
Our blood is boiling
just like the food in this cauldron.
Be quiet.
It will be ready on time, the food will be
ready just like all those soldiers.
Anyway.
I should get going.
I took this duty just to see you.
Know my value.
Come on, leave!
You need battlefield.
May your sword not be wasted.
May Allah help you.
My brave son.
Mother..
I can't hold it anymore let me kiss your hand.
May you be safe on the road.
May Allah help you.
Go now.
Let us go, alps!
Osman Bey, Lord Valens and
Emperor Andronikos have made an alliance.
A huge army of barbarians is present.
This army serves a single purpose.
They won't stop until they banish you
and muslims from this land.
It doesn't matter how many you come.
Gather all armies if you'd like.
Iltutan.
Who are these people?
Let us find out.
But for that..
We need to appear with plain clothes.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
-Where are you going?
-We will visit Yenisehir.
-What are you going to do in Yenisehir?
-What do you think? We were invited to the war.
Osman Bey called for Beys from everywhere.
However..
You seem tired.
Why do you even bother?
We are tired, but not coward.
Alright, alright.
Now you go to Yenisehir
as Osman Bey called you.
I did not ask the important question.
Where do you come from?
We have been riding from Kipcak.
Many of our steed have fallen on the way.
These are what's left.
Kipcak Lands you say?
Kipcak Lands are pretty far away.
-For how many days have you been on road?
-Fifteen.
The calling of Osman Bey..
...is quite recent.
We heard him on the way.
We come, without being called to.
War is always present.
You know the calling,
then why are you sitting here?
Are you running away from the battle?
What do you know?
Maybe I will face them alone?
And I am sitting here before that.
Whatever, don't let me hold you.
Be on your way to Yenisehir.
We will surely meet there.
-If Allah permits.
-Safe travels.
Thank you, you too.
-Goodbye.
-Quickly, we're leaving.
Kipcak Lands..
Oi Praise be!
As long as there are valiants
whose hearts are rooted in this land..
We are in good hands.
They will all be destroyed.
When do you think the battle will begin, brother?
We will be informed, brother.
Osman Bey will inform everyone.
In the name of Allah!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
-Allah is right!
- Allah is eternal!
How is it going, valiants?
-Thank you, Kumral Abdal.
-Thank you.
Praise be!
Just like how your ancestors melted iron..
You are grasping it just as strong.
How did they melt it Kumral Abdal?
Tell us, will you?
A mountain of iron.
Turks want to get out of Ergenekon Plains.
However, everywhere is closed.
They try to find a way.
When they can't find a way..
Their only solution is making way.
To make way..
They start melting the iron mountain.
They lay a line of wood
And a line of coal, in front of the
iron mountain.
They put seventy different fires
to seventy different spots.
The fires raise at the same time.
Iron melts, and makes way.
They find their way.
With unity.
Now, we have such a mountain in front of us.
It may not be iron..
But enemies and traitors confront us.
So we will be one under Osman Bey,
to make path.
We make swords out of the..
...Iron we melted before.
We will make way.
Our children and their children
will walk on this path.
We will be one.
We will unite.
- Allah is eternal.
- Allah is right!
Allah is eternal!
Praise be!
Now it is time to put
these swords in enemies' chests.
- Allah is eternal.
- Allah is right!
Gokcekiz, quickly.
My sisters, now.
O Allah!
Now.
You have to take a step and
take it out using your shoulder.
Use your shoulders with a step.
Now.
Now!
Ya Haqq!
Praise be, praise be!
Wait for a while.
Ready.
Shoot!
Draw!
Get up!
Ready.
Shoot!
If you hold so tight
you will wound your own hand before the enemy.
Hold it softly.
Come on, praise be!
Wait.
The ones who came from
the tribes are being trained my Bala.
Praise be, praise be.
Keep going!
In our tribes, in our cities
whichever stone we lift,
we find hearts that is
yearning for holy war.
That's right.
I wouldn't expect to see
this much as well, Bala.
But we grew bigger.
Our case also grew bigger and spread.
Thank Allah.
It will spread wider, if Allah permits.
It will spread to the walls,
beyond the seas.
Let us be glorious in this battle as well.
I hope so.
Hold it tighter, tighter.
Praise be.
Bala Hatun.
Train with me as well.
Esrigun Hatun, gladly.
Here.
Come on.
Praise be.
I wasn't expecting it.
You are good at sword battle, Bala Hatun.
Thank you.
You are also pretty tough.
It is time!
Brave women of The Sisters!
May my Creator reward you all for your hard work.
Aameen.
I can see that you're getting impatient.
Don't think that I can't see it.
But the patience ends up with soundness.
Even the name of the infidels
will be removed from these lands.
We will plant the banner
of Islam on all of the towers.
Allah is the greatest!
Praise be!
Come on, it is time to renew our vow.
Bring the henna Gokee.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
A warrior's essence resides in sword,
As sacrifice's essence abides in blood.
Soldiers face with a sister's dare,
In martyrdom, they're made aware.
Martyrdom, our breath's embrace,
War courses through our veins with grace.
If sherbet's thirst consumes your desire,
Deceive your heart with martyrdom's fire.
The Sisters, The Sisters!
they bear Fatma Ana's guiding hand
A sister challenges men
in martyrdom's grand.
May Allah bless you.
Before I came to the Frontiers
I was curious about you Sisters the most.
Then
are you ready to fight side by side
with The Sisters, Esrigun Hatun?
I'm ready of course, Bala Hatun.
No, you're not.
Come here.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
You're ready now.
We took an oath,
we do not fight without henna.
Then, since the hennas are ready,
we can set out.
Come on Sisters, to the horses.
The battle awaits us, come on.
My Bey. You brought good news, I hope.
The news is not good.
But we encountered the good on the way.
Lord Valens..
...made an agreement with Emperor Andronikos.
My Bey, why did they make an agreement?
According to the intelligence I've received...
...they built an army by
gathering the most savage soldiers...
...and they are coming on us.
They will be here within the shortest time.
What about the soldiers he called from the west?
Two armies want to unite.
But we will not let that happen.
They are coming at us all together, huh, my Bey?
What are we going to do, my Bey?
We will do the same thing..
...we always did. Bayindir.
We did not stop, and we won't stop.
Conquests will continue.
We will take Koyunhisa
My Bey. We didn't know how powerful they were.
Are we going to fight now although
we know how powerful they are?
Not us.
You will fight, Uraz Bey.
With Demirhan and Ozmen Bey.
Why did we build those catapults?
Why did we send news to the villages?
Now... With the Alps
who will come from the tribes...
...you will take Koyunhisar.
Yes my Bey.
What if they get attacked at that time, my Bey?
No. We will attack the army
which will come from the west.
We will never let those two armies unite.
Come on Beys. What are you waiting for?
Yes my Bey.
My Bey. One army comes from the Constantine
the other comes from the west, right?
Yes.
If we cannot defeat the army
which will come from the west...
...then we cannot defeat Valens' army.
We will split them in two...
...and destroy them.
My Bey.
Do we know something
about the army in the west?
Cerkutay...
Do we? Tell me.
We even know the number
of breaths they take, my Bey.
Good.
My Bey.
This dog has something to tell you.
We will kill you Turks!
You shouldn't have..
Now..
You will choose one of them.
You will..
...tell me everything you know about the army..
...you will tell me, so...
...I can set you free with ransom money.
No, stand up. Come.
Come on now... We just started.
You will tell me.
Stand up, stand up.
Or...
I will beat you to death.
Alright! Alright! I will tell you.
Balaban.
Now go to Yenisehir.
Go to the villages and places around...
...and bring the Alps who gathered for us.
Now that there is a war.
...let them all come!
-Yes my Bey.
-Thank you, thank you.
Alps! Beys.
We will destroy that army...
..before mid-afternoon.
Now listen to me carefully.
The wolf smells its prey.
But it waits for the right time to attack.
But it also makes its move to get it.
We will do the same. Here..
...the army of infidels that we will destroy...
...wants to come to our lands
by passing through Karayurt.
We'll turn the way
into hell for them.
The army will have rest near Kirmagara.
And our mission will start there.
We'll take their
strength first...
..and then their lives.
You'll release their horses.
And the army will have to advance on foot.
They will...
...bring the shields from behind
not to lose their speed.
Baysungur, Shamil.
Aykut.
You will first slow down
the carriage first...
..and then abduct it.
When we take the shields from them.
...they will remain defenseless.
But..
It won't be enough to shoot them with arrows only.
We'll unite with the soldiers coming from Yenisehir...
..and eradicate them.
This sword..
..will stick into your heart.
Commander Mouzalon.
-Leo.
-Sir.
Byzantines ships have been
detected off Yalakova coast.
Your army is coming, sir.
Let's go welcome them.
What about the other troops?
No news yet, but they are coming.
If something goes wrong,
...you will be the first to die, Leo.
The two armies will unite.
That's only how we can take Byzantine back.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
-Hurry up!
-Bring it here.
Sacks here. Sacks here!
Yes, sir.
-Come on!
-Be careful.
Bring it.
Come on! Take it on your back!
Get your troops in order.
Encourage your soldiers with blood and bounty.
Place soldiers around.
Osman shouldn't know about our existence.
Finish all the preparations before
Commander Mouzalon arrives.
Yes, sir.
Move, move!
Come.
You're coming to your end.
My Bey.
Horses got released.
Baysungur sent a message too.
They captured the carriage.
Okay.
Now it's our turn.
Alps.
Prepare the arrows.
Shoot the Turk's arrows!
Now.
-Ya Haqq!
Ya Haqq!
Now it's time to fight!
Come on, sisters!
Allah is the greatest!
-Come on!
-Allah is the greatest!
-Are you alright, my Bey?
-Come on.
Fight, come on!
Whoever sets his eyes on
my land will find his grave there!
Come on, soldiers!
Allah is the greatest!
-They're running off.
-Go!
-Alright.
-Cerkutay!
Come on!
My Bey, why didn't you say
you are Osman Bey?
So what?
-There is no Bey during a fight.
-You're right, my Bey.
-Thank you.
-Live long.
-You too, my Bey.
Live long.
Now it's our turn to move.
You're right, my Bey.
Hurry up, come on!
Bring it over here.
-Get in line!
-Yes, sir.
Of course, sir!
Slow down! Careful!
Commander Mouzalon is coming!
Commander Mouzalon?
Commander Silvanus!
You took a great army with you...
...that was created to destroy Muslims.
Every one of our soldiers...
...will sharpen their swords with Muslim blood, sir.
Very soon.
...I will give them what they want.
The army my friends in the west sent...
..will be here soon.
And then the apocalypse of Turks will begin.
Osman must be celebrating his victory against Nayman,
...without being aware of the apocalypse approaching.
I'm looking forward to seeing the fear in Osman's face...
...when I attack him with my armies.
When Turks see our armies,
...they'll run back to the barren lands where they came from.
For years, they have ravished our lands.
We will show no mercy to them.
We will drive them off from these lands for eternity.
Today, I will bury Turks in the Bafeus Plains.
Bey.
We hit one of the armies.
We don't know the location of the other.
Beys first surround Koyunhisar.
What are we waiting for here?
Forgive me but..
Shall we go join them?
No, the most skilled hunter..
Is the patient one.
Didn't you spend days for one hunt?
I did, Bey, however..
-The animal was in front of us.
-Now it is in front of us as well.
Now we shot them.
We interfered their merging.
Now it is time to hit the army
that Valens brought from Constantinople.
The wounded we let go of will bring us to them.
We will hit them there.
If arrows won't be enough..
Then we will hit them at Koyunhisar Plains.
Let's wait for news first.
Bora, Bora Bora Bora..
This road leads to the plains, I know.
So they are very close.
-Quickly, let us inform my Bey.
-Stop brother, stop.
I know the way. You follow these dogs..
And I will inform Bey.
-Okay brother, quickly.
-Brother.
-Be careful.
-Okay brother, quickly now.
Quickly.
After defeating Osman and his Beys at Bafeos Plains..
The army will continue without resting.
First Yenisehir.
Then Inegol, Sogut and Bilecik.
We will re-take..
Every place we have lost.
In Jesus' name..
We will show no mercy,
no matter who we are facing.
Let the soldiers be prepared.
Where is the army, Leo?
They should've been here by now.
Send someone immediately.
We can not wait for the legion coming from the west.
It is imminent that Osman will know our presence.
We will move immediately.
Cerkutay.
Bey.
As we have guessed,
they are on the way of Yalakova.
Bora is onto them.
Just like that. We are leaving.
Alps, keep your eyes peeled.
We may receive news from
the scouts any moment.
I don't want any flaw.
Inform the surrounding tribes and tell them
to increase the number of scouts.
We take precautions
and leave the rest to Allah.
Yenisehir is our trust.
Come on, get back to your duties.
Yes Malhun Hatun!
Kumral Abdal, what did you do?
The infirmaries are ready.
Our deficiencies have been completed, Malhun Hatun.
I hope we will not need them,
but it is better to take precautions.
May Allah let them have a safe journey.
May He not let the enemies
take any opportunity.
-Ameen.
-I hope so
I will pray too.
I will pray so that my father and
others come back safe and sound.
Pray, of course.
Allah accept the prayers of children,
my beautiful daughter.
My Allah, give strength to my father,
he is Osman Bey
give strength to him,
to my brothers, to his alps.
Give them power, let them defeat the enemy
and make us happy my Allah.
Let my father and his army come back
safe and sound,
let them punish all the evil, aameen.
-Aameen.
Aameen.
Well done, my beautiful daughter.
Are the alps ready, Boran?
All of the alps took up a position my Bey,
they're waiting for your orders.
There are injured men!
What's going on?
Commander
Osman, sir.
Osman attacked us, he destroyed our troop.
Osman! I will drown you with your own blood!
How did it happen?
They attacked suddenly, sir.
There were Turks everywhere.
We couldn't defend ourselves.
How did you survive?
You silly men!
Osman left you alive to spot our place!
Osman is here.
Get the soldiers ready.
We will drown them all with their own blood!
Come here Lord.
This will be your last time.
We will become a glorious state
after we win this war.
I swear..
I swear, from now on,
...we will always attack you!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com